<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BookApp</string>
    <string name="parable">PARABLE OF THE KINGDOM</string>
    <string name="kingdom">The kingdom of heaven is likened to a man who wants to test the paternity of a child (whether the child is his biological son or not). \nSo, he created a new world different and far from his world. He also provided everything he needs to be comfortable and be independent. He then placed this child in this new world. Here is the paternity test: If the child is actually his son, he\'ll be homesick, uncomfortable in this new world because he can\'t live without his father. If the child is not his son, he\'ll be happy and comfortable in this new world. He\'ll explore this world thereby making this new world more comfortable i.e. making it a better place. If you\'re God\'s child, you\'ll be homesick and uncomfortable in this world. You will long to be with your father.</string>
    <string name="twosome_text">I\'ve come to draw a concise conclusion that you can\'t have two things of the same kind;
        you can always have one and not two. \n Hypocrisy will make you believe that you can have a twosome:
        \n      You can\'t have you two bodies. 
        \n      You can\'t have two left brain. \nYou can\'t have two right hands. 
        \n      You can\'t have two left legs. 
        \n      You can\'t have two right ears. 
        \n      You can\'t have two heads. 
        \n      You can\'t have two necks. 
        \n      You can\'t have two lives. 
        \n      You can\'t have two fathers. 
        \n      You can\'t have two mothers. 
        \n      You can\'t serve two masters. 
        \n      You can\'t follow two paths. 
        \n      Matt23vs9. \nLuke16vs13.</string>
    <string name="twosome">TWOSOME</string>
    <string name="hard">People have generalized almost every hard thing (especially relating to Jesus) as being impossible.
        \nImpossible and hard should not be used interchangeably because they don\'t absolutely mean the same thing.
        \nIt is impossible means it is impossible but when it is hard, it means it is hard but possible.
        \nIt is hard but not impossible to be perfect.
        \nIt is hard but not impossible to live without sin.
        \nIt is hard but not impossible to follow in the footsteps of Jesus.
        \nIt is hard but not impossible to do away with lies even \'white lies\'.
        \nIt is hard but not impossible to forsake all and follow Jesus.
        \nIt is hard but not impossible to hate one’s life in this world.
        \nIt is hard but not impossible to call no man on earth father.</string>
    <string name="hard_but_not_impossible">HARD BUT NOT IMPOSSIBLE</string>
    <string name="previous_article">Previous Article</string>
    <string name="next_article">Next Article</string>
    <string name="how_many">How many souls were saved? At least 500 souls were saved during our last annual convention. Hallelujah! 5 souls were saved during the service today, the ministration was powerful. I wonder the yardstick or criteria used to estimate or cipher the number of souls that was saved. Is it by the number of people that fell under the \'anointing\' or spoke in unknown tongues or cried bitterly with a loud voice or what? All these are just gymnastics. Continuous obedience to Jesus teachings only will save you. 31 Jesus therefore said to those Jews that had believed him, If ye abide in my word, then are ye truly my disciples; 32 and ye shall know the truth, and the truth shall make you free. John 8:31-32 He that rejecteth me, and receiveth not my sayings, hath one that judgeth him: the word that I spake, the same shall judge him in the last day. John 12:48 Above all, Jesus said But he that endureth to the end, the same shall be saved. Matt 24:13</string>
    <string name="who_should_name_a_child">The name or tag \'Christians\' is a name generally accepted by the world, it is a name accepted by a group of people who claim to follow Jesus. The name Christian is said to mean \'Christ-like\' --- doing what Christ did. The origin of the tag Christians The first time the name surfaced was 46-48 AD. The disciples were first called Christians in Antioch. Acts 11:26. And when he found him, he brought him to Antioch. So for a whole year Barnabas and Saul met with the church and taught a significant number of people. Now it was in Antioch that the disciples were first called Christians. Acts 11:26 NET The tag Christians was given to believers in Antioch by unbelievers [men, the world]. I wonder why people who supposedly follow Jesus adopt a name given by the world (those that hate Jesus John 7:7; 17:14). The world cannot hate you, but it hates me, because I am testifying about it that its deeds are evil. John 7:7 I have given them your word, and the world has hated them, because they do not belong to the world, just as I do not belong to the world. John 17:14 NET. Who should name a child? A child is named by his or her parents. The parents of a child are obliged to name their child. Let me ask a question here; can you bear a name given to you by people who hate your father? Who should name a believer? A believer is said to be a person that believes in Jesus. So, the person solely obliged to name a believer is Jesus (for all that belongs to God also belongs to Jesus John 17:10) and not the world (the world is controlled by the devil Matt 4:8-9). How will the world (haters of Jesus and His Father John 17:14) name a believers and this believers joyfully accepted the name then and even now? 8 Again, the devil took him to a very high mountain, and showed him all the kingdoms of the world and their grandeur. 9 And he said to him, \'I will give you all these things if you throw yourself to the ground and worship me.\' Matt 4:8-9 NET Jesus said His disciples are not of this world John 17:14. If they are not of this world, they will not associate themselves with the name given by the world. If any disciple of Jesus needs a tag, let him/her go to Jesus words and pick a name. Jesus used many names to qualify his disciples. He called them disciples Matt 10:24, branches John 15:1, sheep John 10:2, friends John 15:15, brothers John 20:17, little flock Luke 12:32, my ecclesia Matt 16:18.</string>
    <string name="who_should">WHO SHOULD NAME A CHILD?</string>
</resources>
